Hello guys, how are you all? If you also
get such a message from any of your fastrack
providers and you have not even used it,
still you get such a message, then
what should you do? We will talk about this in this video, so
I will also show you the ₹1 that was
deducted from me, it has come back, so
how did I do this, I will tell you this in this video,
my fastrack is from ICICI,
its steps will
remain more or less the same, but definitely you will get the resolution, so I do
n't want to miss anything, guys, do
watch this video till the end, I
am your friend Sachin, and let's start this video, so let's
start with this issue, you
can also see in the screenshot, on 9th February,
Sunday, at 1:30, I got this message
that my ₹1.25 has been deducted from my fast
tag. My fast tag was
received through AAA bank and you can also see that
it has been deducted from some Badrabad toll plaza and
my vehicle number is written and it is written 9
In February 2025 and 1156, money was deducted from my Fast Tax and
my balance has gone to -40
and a number is also given in it, if you have any
issue then you can contact on that, so
first of all I thought why did this happen, my
car was kept in the parking lot, I did not even use it
and I was sitting at home on my Sunday
and I thought why did this happen, so
first of all I checked my car, it is
possible that my car might have been stolen, so first of all
I got it checked, as soon as
I went to the parking lot, luckily my car was
there, so I understood that this was a mistake
by ICAC Fast Tax, so to
solve this
you can see their toll free number, you have to
call on it, as you can also see
in this screenshot, I had called them at the
same time and I had talked to them in 3 minutes 49 minutes, so
you also have to simply
call them and as you call, first
you have to select English and Hindi normally,
you can select your preferred language  You
can do it accordingly, then you will get a menu,
from that you have to choose the ninth option, it will be there
that for any fast track related
issue you have to press nine, so you
press nine and your call will be connected
with the customer support, then they will ask you
what is your issue, then you simply tell that
you have received such a message which you have
not used and your vehicle
is with you and you have got a wrong message, then
for verification they can ask you for your customer
ID or your date of birth or your
vehicle number or some other details, so you must
know the date of birth, you already know the
card number, but if they
ask you for the customer ID, then if
you do not know your customer ID, then you have to
call them from the beginning, then you have to
press two which is the option to know the customer ID,
as soon as you press two you will get to know your
customer ID, then
you can call them again by pressing nine, okay,
simply tell your issue, then they will also verify from you
that your vehicle  If there is something, then
give all the information. As soon as
all the information is confirmed, they will
tell you that you will get the resolution in 25 days
and you will get a reference number on your
registered mobile number. As you
can see, I got this referral
number as soon as I complained, so I can track it later through this.
If your
money does not come within 25 days, then you can call this number again and
share this reference number, then
they will take further steps. But you
can see that I had complained to them on
9th February and
my money was credited to me on yesterday i.e. 23rd, ₹1
125. You can also pay it. I have
also given the trip number of the dispute and the amount that was deducted
and this money had come to me.
To confirm this, I
checked the credit, you can check it in any app.
You can see that
I had -40 in Fasttrack and as soon as ₹1 was credited,
my balance became 85, which  Earlier,
you can do this simply and as soon as your
money gets credited, you will get a
message that your issue has been resolved
and the amount will
come to your Fast Track account within 3 days, so mine
came at the same time, so I did not face any such issue, so
you can check it like this also and
if you call on their number and you
can also check your balance by pressing one, then
also you will know that your money has been
credited, as well as this is a bonus, so
you can call them and tell them your balance, your customer
ID and your Fast Track related issue,
as well as if you want to update your vehicle
number or apply for a new Fast
Track or you want to upload your
registration certificate document, then
you will have to select number three,
after which you can also do this thing, so by
calling them you
can solve your complaint, so you
could have done this so simply, so if this video has
helped you even a little,
drop a like in the comment section, that's all
in this video  So thank you so much guys
for watching this video I will definitely see
you in my next video till then
take care guys respect your parents and
elders Jai Hind